# <u>Shakti Dardi</u>

### Deputy Manager-Quality US Healthcare RCM

#### **PROFILE**

9+ Years of experience in Healthcare industry, predominantly in US Healthcare RCM, specialized in Auto Casualty Claim processing/Adjudication, ED and E/M Coding.
4+ Year of Team Management experience both in operations and Quality. Skilled in Client relationship management, Audit and Compliance, Service delivery, process excellence and Employee Engagement. Post graduate in Pharmaceutics, certified professional coder and Six Sigma Certified

#### **CONTACT**

#### **PHONE:**

+918955239275

#### **LINKEDIN:**

Linkedin.com/in/Shakti-dardi

#### **EMAIL:**

Shakti.dardi@gmail.com

#### **LANGUAGE**

\*\*\*\* Hindi \*\*\* English

#### **SKILLS**

**★★★★** Leadership Skills

★★★★ Customer Service

**★★★★★** Communication Skills

**★★★★** Effective Time Management

★★★☆☆ Lean Six Siama

**★★★★** Leadership and Teamwork

**★★★★★ US HealthCare RCM** 

\*\*\*\* ICD 10-CM and CPT Coding

guidelines

★★★★ E/M coding

\*\*\*\* Auto Casualty Claim

Processing/Adjudication

★★★★ MS OFFICE

#### **HOBBIES**

Gardening Cooking Listening to music Watching movies

#### **EDUCATION**

#### University of Rajasthan

July'2012

MSc. In Pharmaceutical Chemistry

#### University of Rajasthan

July'2010

BSc. In Life Sciences with Add-on Subject Biotechnology

#### Senior Secondary School Exam, Rajasthan

June'2006

#### Senior Secondary School Exam, Rajasthan

June'2006

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

**Deputy Manager- Quality** at WNS Global Services PVT LTD July'22-Current

- Managing a team of 30+ QAs across multiple locations
- Managing Day to day audits with leads and AMs
- Ensuring Correct sample size is being audited
- Conducting Brain storming sessions with the team
- Identifying areas of improvement with help of Quality tools
- Leading Calibration between onshore and offshore stake holders
- Monthly SLA deck for Onshore team
- QSD preparation and Ensuring documentation as per ISO

**Assistant Manager-Operations** at WNS Global Services PVT LTD Nov'2020 to June'2022

- Managing a team of 60 FTEs for Auto Casualty Claim processing project, In terms of their production and quality
- Work Allocation Tracking daily incoming volume & Checking due date transactions against the capacity for the day/week/month, reviewing \$LA/TAT
- Client Management, Query resolution & managing and removing roadblocks which may impact the ability for associates to work from home

- Complete administrative tasks such as-attendance, leave regularization, schedule adherence, communication with people, One on One and any training or coaching
- Manage regular Quality checks and provide feedback to the defaulters Review Quality feedback and file rebuttals and provide feedback to the defaulters
- Prepare monthly performance rating and BQ management and discussions Motivated employee performance and satisfaction through fair evaluation, process review and mentoring

**Team lead Quality** US RCM at WNS Global Services PVT LTD Jan'2018 to Oct'2020

- Managing QA team for an Auto Casualty claim processing project across both Nashik and Vizag location
- sample allocation for QA and publishing calibration report to ops for calibration review
- Leading daily calibration call with ops across both the location and discussion on QA findings
- Publishing Weekly/Monthly Quality Dashboard to client and leadership Managing QA coverage for OJT, their Accreditation process, Managing BQ and QA variance
- Re-audit for QA and QC associates, Disseminating Updates and BQ management
- Leading Bi-weekly Client Call and discuss re-audit/ Client reported error findings with Client's QA team

**Quality Analyst** at GeBBS Healthcare Solutions PVT. Ltd. March 2017 – December 2017

- Performing Quality Audits and publish report to ops for calibration
- QA huddle and floor support; disseminating updated and preparing PKTs
- Rebuttals against Re-audits performed by Offshore team
- Steep Knowledge of E/M. ED Profee, ED ACEP Guidelines and Facility; Worked in multiple ED projects

**SR. Medical Coder** at GeBBS Healthcare Solutions PVT. Ltd July 2015 – February 2017

- Worked in many ED and E/M projects
  - specialized in ACEP and CMS coding guidelines
  - Proficient in ICD 10 CM, CPT and HCPCS coding guidelines

**Chemist R & D** at Alchem International Limited December 2013 – June 2015

**Quality Control Chemist** at Gravure Pharmaceuticals PVT LTD, Bhiwadi January 2013 – November 201

#### **CERTIFICATION**

## Intelligence Quality Jan'2022

Lean Six Sigma Black Belt- MSME recognized Certification program

#### AAPC

#### June-2016

Certified Professional Coder